[{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679164587,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":38452,"timeElapsed":348125},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679179077,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":14483,"timeElapsed":362615},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679189906,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":10823,"timeElapsed":373445},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679197536,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":7625,"timeElapsed":381075},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679219996,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":22455,"timeElapsed":403535},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679224774,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":4774,"timeElapsed":408312},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679232006,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":7227,"timeElapsed":415545},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679241379,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":9368,"timeElapsed":424917},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679275700,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":34317,"timeElapsed":459239},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679287354,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":10381,"timeElapsed":470893},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679294406,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":7047,"timeElapsed":477945},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679297560,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3151,"timeElapsed":481099},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679301010,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3445,"timeElapsed":484548},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679304936,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3924,"timeElapsed":488475},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679311332,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":6391,"timeElapsed":494871},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679315394,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":4059,"timeElapsed":498933},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679318722,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3325,"timeElapsed":502260},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679321000,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2273,"timeElapsed":504539},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679325424,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2640,"timeElapsed":508963},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679328120,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2693,"timeElapsed":511659},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679333888,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5765,"timeElapsed":517427},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679335746,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1856,"timeElapsed":519285},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679338184,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2435,"timeElapsed":521722},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679340937,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2751,"timeElapsed":524476},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679352306,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":11366,"timeElapsed":535845},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679355272,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2963,"timeElapsed":538811},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679369666,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":14391,"timeElapsed":553205},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679381379,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":5481,"timeElapsed":564918},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679390692,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":9310,"timeElapsed":574231},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679394886,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4192,"timeElapsed":578425},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679396786,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1898,"timeElapsed":580325},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679398881,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2092,"timeElapsed":582420},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679401686,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2799,"timeElapsed":585225},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679404515,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2827,"timeElapsed":588054},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679406728,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2208,"timeElapsed":590266},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679408541,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1811,"timeElapsed":592080},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679421140,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":10607,"timeElapsed":604678},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679423112,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1968,"timeElapsed":606651},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679424696,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1581,"timeElapsed":608235},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679426594,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1892,"timeElapsed":610133},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679428144,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1545,"timeElapsed":611683},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679430684,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2536,"timeElapsed":614223},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679432576,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1889,"timeElapsed":616115},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679434203,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1623,"timeElapsed":617742},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679435886,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1680,"timeElapsed":619425},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679442192,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":6301,"timeElapsed":625731},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679445774,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2304,"timeElapsed":629313},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679447348,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1571,"timeElapsed":630887},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679448814,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1461,"timeElapsed":632353},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679450552,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1735,"timeElapsed":634091},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679467086,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":16531,"timeElapsed":650625},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679471409,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4320,"timeElapsed":654948},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679473228,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1816,"timeElapsed":656767},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679475494,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2261,"timeElapsed":659032},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679477517,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2018,"timeElapsed":661055},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679479338,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1818,"timeElapsed":662877},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679489104,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":8719,"timeElapsed":672643},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679490450,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1342,"timeElapsed":673988},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679493782,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3329,"timeElapsed":677320},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679496090,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2303,"timeElapsed":679628},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679497818,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1724,"timeElapsed":681357},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679504411,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":6589,"timeElapsed":687950},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679512677,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":8264,"timeElapsed":696216},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679515815,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3135,"timeElapsed":699354},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679519212,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3394,"timeElapsed":702750},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679528578,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":4420,"timeElapsed":712117},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679530432,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":1852,"timeElapsed":713971},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679546728,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":16292,"timeElapsed":730267},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679553984,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":7254,"timeElapsed":737523},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679560429,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":6443,"timeElapsed":743968},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679562302,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":1870,"timeElapsed":745841},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679564406,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2099,"timeElapsed":747945},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679566901,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2490,"timeElapsed":750440},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679569231,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2325,"timeElapsed":752770},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679581037,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":10483,"timeElapsed":764576},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679583848,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2808,"timeElapsed":767387},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679590319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":6468,"timeElapsed":773858},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679593059,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2736,"timeElapsed":776598},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679598856,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":5791,"timeElapsed":782395},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679603129,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":4269,"timeElapsed":786668},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679607762,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":4628,"timeElapsed":791301},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679611950,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":4184,"timeElapsed":795489},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679614549,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2597,"timeElapsed":798088},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679617640,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2111,"timeElapsed":801179},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679619326,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":1683,"timeElapsed":802865},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679621070,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":1739,"timeElapsed":804609},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679623623,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2551,"timeElapsed":807162},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679629314,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":5687,"timeElapsed":812853},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679634410,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":5093,"timeElapsed":817949},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679636588,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2174,"timeElapsed":820127},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679638384,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":1793,"timeElapsed":821923},{"subjectID":"d8dm0m4eba","prolificID":"673a53fc2a05c93edf027ccd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b42be8c45f367d25a75","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679641210,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2823,"timeElapsed":824749}]